她的DNA不只是重新排列了
Her DNA didn't just rearrange --
还加入了额外的大分子链
It contains extra macromolecules.
我都不知道还有这种可能性
I wouldn't think that even possible.
-太神奇了  -太可怕了
- That's amazing. - It's horrific.
我们得确保你没受到任何污染
We need to make sure that you're not contaminated
或者感染
or infected in any way.
最坏的情况是什么
What's the worst that could happen?
一场瘟疫
An epidemic.
这结论太吓人了吧
That's a pretty harsh conclusion.
我觉得我有责任
Well, and I feel responsible.
我们都有
We all do.
你当时不可能做什么
There's nothing you could have done.
我本来可以的
Yes, there was.
我对超能力和外星生物学太好奇了
I was so curious about powers, about unearthly biology,
我好奇它会引我们到何处
wondering where it might lead,